Guide to the Frauke Heard-Bey and David Heard collection AD.MC.064
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- Periodicals and news digests, 1972-2015
  - News digest services: A.P.S. Diplomat and A.P.S. Review (Beirut / Nicosia: Arab Press Service), 1982-2002
    - APS Review: Gas Market Trends
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 24, Nos. 1-25; Vol. 25, Nos. 1-7, 9-25, January - December 1985 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 26, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 27, Nos. 1-2, 4-7, 9-26, January - December 1986 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 28, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 29, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1987 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 30, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 31, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1988 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 32, Nos. 5-26; Vol. 33, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1989 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 34, Nos. 1-4, 6-7, 9-26; Vol. 35, Nos. 1-26 [with gaps], January - December 1990 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 36, Nos. 1-8, 10-26; Vol. 37, Nos. 1-2, 4-26, January - December 1991 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 38, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 39, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1992 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 40, Nos. 1-3, 5-11, 14-22, 24-26; Vol. 41, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1993 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 42, Nos. 1-21; Vol. 43, Nos. 2-26, January - December 1994 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 44, nos. 1-7, 9-26; Vol. 45, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1995 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 46, No.1-3, 6-23, 25-26; Vol. 47, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1996 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 48, Nos. 1-16, 19-26, January - June 1997 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 53, no. 21, 23, 24-26, November - December 1999 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 54, Nos. 1-19, 22, 25-26; Vol. 55, Nos. 1-7, January - June 2000 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 56, Nos. 17-26; Vol. 57, Nos. 1-19, 21-24, 26, April - December 2001 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Gas Market Trends, Vol. 58, Nos. 4, 6-14, 16-26; Vol. 59, Nos. 1-2, 7-11, January - September 2002 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - APS Review: Miscellaneous
      - APS Conferences, 1988-2001 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - APS Review: Investments and Finance, Volume 20 Index, No. 1 - 5, January - June 1983 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - APS Review: Investments and Finance, Volume 21 Index, No. 1, 3 - 6, July - December 1983 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - APS Review: Oil Market Trends
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 20, Nos. 1-2, 4-26; Vol. 21, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1983 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 22, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 23, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1984 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 24, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 25, Nos. 1-7, 9-26, January - December 1985 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 26, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 27, Nos. 2-26, January - December 1986 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 28. Nos. 1-26; Vol. 29, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1987 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 30, Nos. 1-26; Vol. 31, Nos. 1-25, January - December 1988 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 32, Nos. 4-26; Vol. 33, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1989 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 34, Nos. 1-4, 6-7, 9-26; Vol. 35, Nos. 1-10, 13-19, 21-22, 24-26, January - December 1990 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 36, Nos. 1-8, 10-21, 23-25; Vol. 37, Nos. 1-2, 4-26, January - December 1991 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 38, Nos.1-14, 16, 19-26; Vol. 39, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1992 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 40, Nos. 1-3, 5-11, 14-22, 24-26; Vol. 41, Nos. 1-19, 21-26, January - December 1993 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 42, Nos. 1-21; Vol. 43, Nos. 2-26, January - December 1994 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 44, Nos. 1-7, 9-26; Vol. 45, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1995 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 46, Nos. 1-4, 6-23, 25-26; Vol. 47, Nos. 1-26, January - December 1996 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 48, Nos. 1-17, 19-26, January - June 1997 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 53, Nos. 21-26, November - December 1999 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 54, Nos. 2-19, 22. 25-26; Vol. 55, Nos. 1-7, January - August 2000 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 56, Nos. 17-26; Vol. 57, Nos. 1-19, 21-25, 26, April - December 2001 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Oil Market Trends, Vol. 58, Nos. 3-26; Vol. 59, Nos. 1-2, 8-11, January - September 2002 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - News digest services: GulfWire (Washington: National Council on U.S.-Arab Relations, and U.S. - GCC Corporate Cooperation Committee), 2000-2002
    - Bulletins and announcements, March - December 2001 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Calendar Supplements, January - September 2001 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Items of Interest, October 2001 - April 2002 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Perspectives, March 2001 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Perspectives, April - June 2001 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Perspectives, July - September 2001 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Perspectives, October - December 2001 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Perspectives, January - March 2002 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Perspectives, April - May 2002 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Special Supplements (and reports), June - October 2000 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Special Supplements (and reports), January - March 2001 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Special Supplements (and reports), April - June 2001 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Special Supplements (and reports), July - September, November 2001 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Special Supplements (and reports), January - May 2002 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Voices of the Region, February - March 2001 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Voices of the Region, April - June 2001 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Voices of the Region, July - September 2001 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Voices of the Region, October - December 2001 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Voices of the Region, January - March 2002 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Voices of the Region, April - May 2002 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #51-55, June - July 2000 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #56-60, August 2000 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #61-64, September 2000 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #65-67, 69, 77, October - December 2000 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #78-81, January 2001 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #82-88, February - March 2001 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #89-93, April 2001 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #94, 96-98, May 2001 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #99-102, June 2001 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #103-107, July 2001 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #108-111, August 2001 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #112-114, September 2001 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #115-117, 119, October 2001 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #123-125, November - December 2001 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #129-131, January 2002 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #133-136, February 2002 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #137-139, March 2002 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #140-142, April 2002 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Weekly e-Newsletter, #144-146, May 2002 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Prospectus (slide show images, sample newsletter articles), undated, circa 2000 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - News digest services: Middle East Economic Survey (MEES): A Weekly Review of News and Views on Middle East Oil (Beirut / Nicosia: Middle East Petroleum and Economic Publications), 1972-2000
    - Volume XV no. 39 Supplement, 21 July 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Volume XVI no. 38, 13 July 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Volume XXIII, No. 11, December 31, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Volume XXIII, Nos. 12-15, January 7 - 28, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Volume XXIII, Nos. 16-19, February 4 - 25, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Volume XXIII, Nos. 20-24, March 3 - 31, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Volume XXIII, Nos. 25-28, April 7 - 28, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Volume XXIII, Nos. 29-32, May 5 - 26, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Volume XXIII, Nos. 33-37, June 2 - 30, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Volume XXIII, Nos. 38-41, July 7 - 28, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Volume XXIII, Nos. 42-45, August 4 - 25, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Volume XXIII, Nos. 46-52, September 1 - 29, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Volume XXIII, Nos. 51-52; Volume XXIV, Nos. 1-2, October 6 - 27, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Volume XXIV, Nos. 3-5, November 3 - 17, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Volume XXIV, Nos. 7-11, December 1 - 29, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Volume XXIV, Nos. 12-15, January 5 - 26, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Volume XXIV, Nos. 16-19, February 2 - 23, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Volume XXIV, Nos. 20-24, March 2 - 30, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Volume XXIV, Nos. 25-28, April 6 - 27, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Volume XXIV, Nos. 29-32, May 4 - 25, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Volume XXIV, Nos. 33-37, June 1 - 29, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Volume XXIV, Nos. 38-41, July 6 - 27, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Volume XXIV, Nos. 42-46, August 3 - 31, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Volume XXIV, Nos. 47-49, September 7 - 21, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Volume XXIV, Nos. 51-52; Volume XXV, Nos. 1-2, October 5 - 26, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Volume XXV, Nos. 3-7, November 2 - 30, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Volume XXV, Nos. 8-11, December 7 - 28, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Volume XXV, Nos. 12-15, January 4 - 25, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Volume XXV, Nos. 16-19, February 1 - 22, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Volume XXV, Nos. 20-24, March 8 - 29, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Volume XXV, Nos. 25-28, April 5 - 26, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Volume XXV, Nos. 29-33, May 3 - 31, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Volume XXV, Nos. 34-37, June 7 - 28, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Volume XXV, Nos. 38, 40-41, July 5 - 26, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Volume XXV, Nos. 42-46, August 2 - 30, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Volume XXV, Nos. 47-50, September 6 - 27, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Volume XXV, Nos. 51-52; Volume XXVI, Nos. 1-2, October 4 - 25, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Volume XXVI, Nos. 3-7, November 1 - 29, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Volume XXVI, Nos. 8-11, December 6 - 27, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Volume XXVI, Nos. 12-16, January 3 - 31, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Volume XXVI, Nos. 17-20, February 7 - 28, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Volume XXVI, Nos. 21-24, March 7 - 28, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Volume XXVI, Nos. 25-28, April 4 - 25, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Volume XXVI, Nos. 29-33, May 2 - 30, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Volume XXVI, Nos. 34-37, June 6 - 27, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Volume XXVI, Nos. 38-41, July 4 - 25, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Volume XXVI, Nos. 42-46, August 1 - 29, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Volume XXVI, Nos. 47-50, September 5 - 26, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Volume XXVI, Nos. 50-52; Volume XXVII, Nos. 1-3, October 3 - 31, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Volume XXVII, Nos. 4-7, November 7 - 28, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Volume XXVII, Nos. 8-11, December 5 - 26, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Volume XXVII, Nos. 12-16, January 2 - 30, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Volume XXVII, Nos. 17-20, February 6 - 27, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Volume XXVII, Nos. 21-24, March 5 - 26, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Volume XXVII, Nos. 25-29, April 2 - 30, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Volume XXVII, Nos. 30-33, May 7 - 28, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Volume XXVII, Nos. 34-37, June 4 - 25, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Volume XXVII, Nos. 38-42, July 2 - 30, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Volume XXVII, Nos. 42-46, August 6 - 27, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Volume XXVII, Nos. 47-50, September 3 - 24, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Volume XXVII, Nos. 51-52; Volume XXVIII, Nos. 1-3, October 1 -29, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Volume XXVIII, Nos. 4-7, November 5 - 26, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Volume XXVIII, Nos. 8-12, December 3 - 31, 1984 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Volume XXVIII, Nos. 13-16, January 7 - 28, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Volume XXVIII, Nos. 17-20, February 4 - 25, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Volume XXVIII, Nos. 21-24, March 4 - 25, 1985 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Volume XXVIII, Nos. 25-29, April 1 - 29, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Volume XXVIII, Nos. 30-33, May 6 - 27, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Volume XXVIII, Nos. 34-37, June 3 - 24, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Volume XXVIII, Nos. 38-42, July 1 - 29, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Volume XXVIII, Nos. 43-46, August 5 - 26, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Volume XXVIII Nos. 47-51, September 2 - 30, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Volume XXVIII, Nos. 52, Volume XXIX, Nos. 1-3, October 7 - 28, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Volume XXIX, Nos. 4-7, November 4 - 25, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Volume XXIX, Nos. 8-12, December 2 - 30, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Volume XXIX, Nos. 13-16, January 6 - 27, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Volume XXIX, Nos. 17-20, February 3 - 24, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Volume XXIX, Nos. 21-25, March 3 - 31, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Volume XXIX, Nos. 26-29, April 7 - 28, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Volume XXIX, Nos. 30-33, May 5 - 26, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Volume XXIX, Nos. 34-38, June 2 - 30, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Volume XXIX, Nos. 39-42, July 7 - 28, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Volume XXIX, Nos. 43-46, August 4 - 25, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Volume XXIX, Nos. 47-51, September 1 - 29, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Volume XXIX, No. 52; Volume XXX, Nos. 1-3, October 6 - 27, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Volume XXX, Nos. 4-7, November 3 - 24, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Volume XXX, Nos. 8-12, December 1 - 29, 1986 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Volume XXX, Nos. 13-16, January 5 - 26, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Volume XXX, Nos. 17-20, February 2 -23, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Volume XXX, Nos. 22-25, March 2 - 30, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Volume XXX, Nos. 26-29, April 6 - 27, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Volume XXX, Nos. 30-33, May 4 -25, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Volume XXX, Nos. 34-38, June 1 - 29, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Volume XXX, Nos. 39-42, July 6 - 27, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Volume XXX, Nos. 43-47, August 3 - 31, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Volume XXX, Nos. 48-51, September 7 - 28, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Volume XXX, No. 52; Volume XXXI Nos. 1-3, October 5 - 26, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Volume XXXI, Nos. 4-8, November 2 - 30, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Volume XXXI, Nos. 9-12, December 7 - 28, 1987 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Volume XXXI nos. 13-16, January 4 - 25, 1988 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Volume XXXI, Nos. 17-21, February 1 -29, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Volume XXXI, Nos. 22-25, March 7 - 28, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Volume XXXI, Nos. 26-29, April 4 - 25, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Volume XXXI, Nos. 30-34, May 2 - 30, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Volume XXXI, Nos. 35-38, June 6 - 27, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Volume XXXI, Nos. 39-42, July 4 - 25, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Volume XXXI, Nos. 43-47, August 1 - 29, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Volume XXXI, Nos. 48-51, September 5 - 26, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Volume XXXI, No. 52, Volume XXXII, Nos. 1-4, October 3 - 31, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Volume XXXII, Nos. 5-8, November 7 - 28, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Volume XXXII, Nos. 9-13, December 5 - 26, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Volume XXXII, Nos. 14-17, January 9 -30, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Volume XXXII, Nos. 18-21, February 6 - 27, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Volume XXXII, Nos. 22-25, March 6 - 27, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Volume XXXII, Nos. 26-29, April 3 - 24, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Volume XXXII, Nos. 30-34, May 1 - 29, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Volume XXXII, Nos. 35-38, June 5 - 26, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Volume XXXII, Nos. 39-43, July 3 - 31, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Volume XXXII, Nos. 44-47, August 7 - 28, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Volume XXXII, Nos. 48-51, September 4 - 25, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Volume XXXII, No. 52; Volume XXXIII, Nos. 1-4, October 2 - 30, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Volume XXXIII, Nos. 5-8, November 6 - 27, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Volume XXXIII, Nos. 9-13, December 4 - 25, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Volume XXXIII, Nos. 14-17, January 8 - 29, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Volume XXXIII, Nos. 18-21, February 5 - 26, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Volume XXXIII, Nos. 22-25, March 5 - 26, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Volume XXXIII, Nos. 26-30, April 2 - 30, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Volume XXXIII, Nos. 31-34, May 7 - 28, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Volume XXXIII, Nos. 36-38, June 4 - 25, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Volume XXXIII, Nos. 39-43, July 2 - 30, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Volume XXXIII, Nos. 44-47, August 6 - 27, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Volume XXXIII, Nos. 48-51, September 3 - 24, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Volume XXXIII, No. 52, Volume XXXIV, Nos. 1-4, October 1 - 29, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Volume XXXIV, Nos. 5 - 8, November 5 - 26, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Volume XXXIV, Nos. 9 - 13, December 3 - 31, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Volume XXXIV, Nos. 14-17, January 7 - 28, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Volume XXXIV, Nos. 18 - 21, February 4 - 25, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Volume XXXIV, Nos. 22-25, March 4 - 25, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Volume XXXIV, Nos. 26 - 30, April 1 - 29, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Volume XXXIV, Nos. 31-34, May 6 - 27, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Volume XXXIV, Nos. 35-38, June 3 - 24, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Volume XXXIV, Nos. 39-43, July 1 - 29, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Volume XXXIV, Nos. 44-47, August 5 - 26, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Volume XXXIV, Nos. 48-52, September 2 - 30, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Volume XXXV, Nos. 1-4, October 7 - 28, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Volume XXXV, Nos. 5-8, November 4 - 25, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Volume XXXV, Nos. 9-13, December 2 - 30, 1991 (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Volume XXXV, Nos. 14-17, January 6 - 27, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Volume XXXV, Nos. 18-21, February 3 - 24, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Volume XXXV, Nos. 22-26, March 2 - 30, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - Volume XXXV, Nos. 27-29, April 6 - 20, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - Volume XXXV, Nos. 30-34, May 4 - 25, 1992 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - Volume XXXV, Nos. 35, 37-39, June 1 - 29, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Volume XXXV, Nos. 40-43, July 6 - 27, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Volume XXXV, Nos. 44-48, August 3 - 31, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Volume XXXV, Nos. 49-52, September 7 - 28, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Volume XXXVI, Nos. 1-4, October 5 - 26, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Volume XXXVI, Nos. 5-9, November 2 - 30, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Volume XXXVI, Nos. 10-14, December 7 - 28, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Volume XXXVI, Nos. 15-17, January 11 - 25, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Volume XXXVI, Nos. 18-21, February 1 - 22, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Volume XXXVI, Nos. 22-26, March 1 - 29, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Volume XXXVI, Nos. 27-30, April 5 - 26, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Volume XXXVI, Nos. 31-35, May 3 - 31, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Volume XXXVI, Nos. 36-39, June 7 - 28, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Volume XXXVI, Nos. 40-43, July 5 - 26, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Volume XXXVI, Nos. 44-48, August 2 - 30, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Volume XXXVI, Nos. 49-52, September 6 - 27, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Volume XXXVII, Nos. 1-4, October 4 - 25, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Volume XXXVII, Nos. 5-9, November 1 - 29, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Volume XXXVII, Nos. 10-14, December 6 - 27, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Volume XXXVII, Nos. 15-18, January 10 - 31, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Volume XXXVII, Nos.19-22, February 7- 28, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Volume XXXVII, Nos. 23-26, March 7 - 28, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Volume XXXVII, Nos. 27-30, April 4 - 25, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Volume XXXVII, Nos. 31-35, May 2 - 30 1994 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Volume XXXVII, Nos. 36-39, June 6 - 27, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Volume XXXVII, Nos. 40-43, July 4 - 25, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Volume XXXVII, Nos. 44-48, August 1 - 29, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Volume XXXVII, Nos. 49-52, September 5 - 26, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Volume XXXVIII, Nos. 1-5, October 3 - 31, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Volume XXXVIII, Nos. 6-9, November 7 - 28, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Volume XXXVIII, Nos. 10-14, December 5 - 26, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Volume XXXVIII, Nos. 15-18, January 9 - 30, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Volume XXXVIII, Nos. 19-22, February 6-27, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Volume XXXVIII, Nos. 23-26, March 6 - 27, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Volume XXXVIII, Nos. 27-30, April 3 - 24, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Volume XXXVIII, Nos. 31-35, May 1 -29, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Volume XXXVIII, Nos. 36-39, June 5 - 26, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Volume XXXVIII, Nos. 40-44, July 3 - 31, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Volume XXXVIII, Nos. 45-48, August 7 - 28, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Volume XXXVIII, Nos. 49-52, September 4 - 25, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 1-5, October 2 - 30, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 6-9, November 6 - 27, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 10-14, December 4 - 25, 1995 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 15-18, January 1996 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 19-22, February 5 - 26, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 24-26, March 11 - 25, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 27-31, April 1 - 29, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 32-35, May 6 - 27, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 37-39, June 10 - 24, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 40-44, July 1 - 29, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 45-48, August 5 - 26, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 49-53, September 2 - 30, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 54-57, October 7 - 28, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 58-61, November 4 - 25, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Volume XXXIX, Nos. 62-66, December 9 - 30, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Volume XL, Nos. 1-4, January 6 - 27, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Volume XL, Nos. 5-8, February 3 - 24, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Volume XL, Nos. 9-13, March 3 - 31, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Volume XL, Nos. 14-17, April 7 - 28, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Volume XL, Nos. 18-21, May 5 - 26, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Volume XL, Nos. 22-26, June 2 - 30, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Volume XL, Nos. 27-30, July 7 - 28, 1997 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - Volume XL, Nos. 31-34, August 4 - 25, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Volume XL ,No. 35-39, September 1 - 29, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Volume XL, Nos. 40-43, October 6 - 27, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Volume XL, Nos. 44-47, November 3 - 24, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Volume XL, Nos. 48 - 51/52, December 1 - 29, 1997 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Volume XLI, Nos. 1 - 4, January 5 -26, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Volume XLI, Nos. 5-8, February 2 - 23, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Volume XLI, Nos. 9-13, March 2 - 30, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Volume XLI, Nos. 13-17, April 6 - 27, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 9)